(Amy:)Well, there was the time
I had my tonsils out,
(Amy:)and I shared a room with
a little Vietnamese girl.
(Amy:)She didn't make it
through the night,
(Amy:)but up till then,
it was kind of fun.
(Penny:)Okay. Well, I guess we're
having a slumber party.
(Penny:)Oh!
(Amy:)Pillow fight!
(Leonard:)Oh, I hope they
let us in soon.
(Leonard:)I'm tired of running to the gas
station to use the bathroom.
(Leonard:)The guy makes me buy
a Gatorade every time.
(Leonard:)It's a vicious circle.
(Howard:)Too bad you don't have
a stadium pal like me.
(Leonard:)What's a stadium pal?
Let me put it this way:
(Howard:)takes care of
the bathroom problem,
(Howard:)and it keeps your calf warm.
(Raj:)Hey, guys, bad news.
I just did a quick calculation.
Given the size of the theater
and the length of this line,
(Raj:)we might not get seats.
(Sheldon:)What did he say?
(Leonard:)Nice going, Raj.
(Leonard:)Just got him down for his nap.